{
    "subject": "resource/Cercospora_apii",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/linguistics/gold/hypernym",
    "object": "resource/Pathogen",
    "human_readable": "Cercospora apii is a type of Pathogen.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9722638726234436,
            "question": "What makes Cercospora apii a unique type of pathogen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.889619767665863,
            "question": "What kind of organism is Cercospora apii?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8317928314208984,
            "question": "What are some examples of diseases caused by pathogens like Cercospora apii?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8043228387832642,
            "question": "How do pathogens such as Cercospora apii spread?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6653785109519958,
            "question": "What is the impact of pathogens like Cercospora apii on agriculture?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6257128715515137,
            "question": "Can Cercospora apii infect humans or animals?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6137861609458923,
            "question": "What type of environment does Cercospora apii typically thrive in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6071390509605408,
            "question": "Are there any control measures for diseases caused by Cercospora apii?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5148801207542419,
            "question": "Are there any specific plants that are particularly susceptible to infection by Cercospora apii?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4897092580795288,
            "question": "Can Cercospora apii cause disease in plants?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Cercospora apii is a type of Pathogen.",
            "html": "dbpedia_193_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any specific plants that are particularly susceptible to infection by Cercospora apii?",
            "html": "dbpedia_193_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any control measures for diseases caused by Cercospora apii?",
            "html": "dbpedia_193_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of environment does Cercospora apii typically thrive in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_193_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_193_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_193_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_193_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_193_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_193_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_193_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_193_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_193_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_193_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_193_80.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents supports that Cercospora apii is identified as a pathogen. Specifically, one document mentions \"Cercospora apiI Early Blight: celery (Apium graveolens var.)\", which indicates it causes a disease on celery, thus confirming its status as a pathogen."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}